<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>danielblog</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Collection of blog posts of experiences from Daniel van Paassen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/cropped-cropped-Singapore_place-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>danielblog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</title>
		<link>/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/?utm_source=rss#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=malaysia-kuala-lumpur</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[danielhonderd]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=276</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I expected to have a culture shock as big as the one that I experienced when I went to the USA for my exchange. Even though this is indeed what I saw, it was less than I expected, probably because of the fact that we brought a part of NL with us (the 31 other&#8230;&#160;<a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I expected to have a culture shock as big as the one that I experienced when I went to the USA for my exchange. Even though this is indeed what I saw, it was less than I expected, probably because of the fact that we brought a part of NL with us (the 31 other people). Kuala Lumpur is a vibrant, warm, and diverse city. We were told of the local customs, of for example wearing long pants or pointing with the thumb instead of index finger out of respect. We resided in a hotel and could explore the city from there using cheap Uber rides (with the app called Grab). The food was definitely more spicy, and it took some getting used to, but it was also delicious and a hot topic in the culture we experienced.&nbsp;</p>



<p>One of the places we went to was the Batu Caves, where I rock-climbed with some others and saw a beautiful Indian temple.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Climbing-the-Batu-Cave-577x1024-640x480.jpg" title="Climbing-the-Batu-Cave" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>We also visited a company called Juristech, and enjoyed the things to see and do in China Town. There was also a butterfly dome we visited, where many pretty pictures where taken.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/On-the-monorail-649x1024-640x480.jpg" title="On-the-monorail" alt="" /></div></div><p>The post <a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Post!</title>
		<link>/2023/07/14/first-post/?utm_source=rss#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=first-post</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[danielhonderd]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In just one week, my adventure begins as I embark on a Study Trip organized by my study association. I feel incredibly lucky to be one of the 31 students chosen for this trip across Asia. Our journey will span three weeks, taking us to Kuala Lumpur, Singapore, and Bandung. During our trip, we&#8217;ll have&#8230;&#160;<a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">First Post!</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/">First Post!</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In just one week, my adventure begins as I embark on a Study Trip organized by my study association. I feel incredibly lucky to be one of the 31 students chosen for this trip across Asia. Our journey will span three weeks, taking us to Kuala Lumpur, Singapore, and Bandung.</p>



<p>During our trip, we&#8217;ll have the opportunity to explore fascinating destinations, visit universities and businesses, and immerse ourselves in different cultures. From the bustling streets of Kuala Lumpur to the vibrant city-state of Singapore and the scenic beauty of Bandung, each location promises unique experiences and unforgettable memories.</p>



<p>The Study Visit Committee has meticulously planned our daily itineraries, ensuring a diverse range of activities and excursions. We&#8217;ll have the chance to delve into local cuisines, discover hidden gems, and engage with the vibrant communities we encounter along the way.<br>Additionally, the committee has organized lunch lectures and in-house days at various companies, which not only provide us with valuable insights but also serve as a source of income for part of the trip&#8217;s finances.</p>



<p>As we embark on this journey together, let&#8217;s make it a trip to remember for all the right reasons. From breathtaking sights to enriching cultural encounters, we&#8217;ll seize every moment and create lifelong memories. The countdown has begun, and I can&#8217;t wait to embark on this incredible adventure in just one week&#8217;s time!</p><p>The post <a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/">First Post!</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
