<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>danielblog</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Collection of blog posts of experiences from Daniel van Paassen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:16:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/cropped-cropped-Singapore_place-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>danielblog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Singapore</title>
		<link>/2023/08/27/singapore/?utm_source=rss#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=singapore</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[danielhonderd]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardens by the Bay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, the country where everything is forbidden. Before entering, we found out that there are a plethora of strict laws in place, that might even mean jail or the death sentence. Drugs were extremely forbidden, but fake cigarettes too (e-cigarette for example). Everyone seems to have a job here, and the streets are extremely clean&#8230;&#160;<a href="/2023/08/27/singapore/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">Singapore</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/2023/08/27/singapore/">Singapore</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, the country where everything is forbidden. Before entering, we found out that there are a plethora of strict laws in place, that might even mean jail or the death sentence. Drugs were extremely forbidden, but fake cigarettes too (e-cigarette for example). Everyone seems to have a job here, and the streets are extremely clean (chewing gum is also forbidden). </p>



<p>On the first day we arrived in the afternoon to stash our bags in the hostel upon arrival. That same evening we went to the gardens by the bay shopping mall to go to the casino.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/What-does-my-watch-say-1024x768-640x480.jpg" title="What does my watch say" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>Also in Singapore we enjoyed the delicious cuisine that was offered to us, although the type of food was similar to what we could get in Kuala Lumpur. There were less outdoor food stands here however. The dinner location for the first night was organized by the committee, at a food court. A place where different food stands were placed around shared dining places, you could get a tray with food at whichever cuisine you wanted and still eat together. </p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/A-food-stand-at-the-food-court-1024x768-640x480.jpg" title="A food stand at the food court" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>We also saw a lot of nature here, we did a trip to the botinical garden and took beautiful pictures there. There was also the more adventourus plan by Lieke, Max and Gina to do a mini hike (part of the Macritchie treetop trail). Remember how you shouldn&#8217;t have food out when there&#8217;s monkeys around? Apparently they can be quite hidden, poor Stan lost his only lunch option that day.  Afterwards we went to Palau Ibun to rent bikes and see mangrove trees. This Palau Island had ferries going there, and luckily we had enough cash for the outward journey! <a href="https://emojipedia.org/person-facepalming"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f926.png" alt="🤦" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></a></p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Jumping-away-from-my-problems-577x1024-640x480.jpg" title="Jumping away from my problems" alt="" /></div></div>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-6 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow"></div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow">
<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/At-the-botanical-garden.mp4"></video></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow"></div>
</div>



<p>We visited a Chinese opera, which was very interesting but also very difficult to appreciate a lot since I had not seen something similar in my life before. We had a company visit to a quantum startup event, which was hosted at the Microsoft experience center. Another fun activity I did was visiting the flower dome at gardens by the bay, which had sections divided as the different continents, and then vegetation of each specific continent there.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Posing-1024x768-640x480.jpg" title="Posing" alt="" /></div></div>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-10 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow">
<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chinese-opera.mp4"></video></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow">
<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Poking-around-at-Microsoft.mp4"></video></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow">
<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Insert-theme-song.mp4"></video></figure>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="/2023/08/27/singapore/">Singapore</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/At-the-botanical-garden.mp4" length="6841533" type="video/mp4" />
<enclosure url="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chinese-opera.mp4" length="18186919" type="video/mp4" />
<enclosure url="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Poking-around-at-Microsoft.mp4" length="1216903" type="video/mp4" />
<enclosure url="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Insert-theme-song.mp4" length="57012830" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</title>
		<link>/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/?utm_source=rss#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=malaysia-kuala-lumpur</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[danielhonderd]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monkeys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study Visit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trip]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=276</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I expected to have a culture shock as big as the one that I experienced when I went to the USA for my exchange. Even though this is indeed what I saw, it was less than I expected, probably because of the fact that we brought a part of NL with us (the 31 other&#8230;&#160;<a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I expected to have a culture shock as big as the one that I experienced when I went to the USA for my exchange. Even though this is indeed what I saw, it was less than I expected, probably because of the fact that we brought a part of NL with us (the 31 other people). Kuala Lumpur is a vibrant, warm, and diverse city. We were told of the local customs, of for example wearing long pants or pointing with the thumb instead of index finger out of respect. We resided in a hotel and could explore the city from there using cheap Uber rides (with the app called Grab). </p>



<p>One of the places we went to was the Batu Caves, where I rock-climbed with some others and saw a beautiful Indian temple. Here we also found a lot of monkeys. The only thing you&#8217;d have to watch out for is having food out in the open.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Climbing-the-Batu-Cave-1-577x1024-640x480.jpg" title="Climbing-the-Batu-Cave-1" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>We also visited a company called Juristech, they showed us around and had organized a delicious lunch for us to try the Malay cuisine.</p>



<div class="wp-block-group is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-16 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:30%"></div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow">
<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls loop muted src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Food-at-Juristech-company-1.mp4"></video></figure>
</div>



<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:30%"></div>
</div>
</div></div>



<p>On the topic of food, it was clear to me that I had to quickly adapt to enjoy spice (normally I don&#8217;t even put sambal on my döner). But all Malay/Indian/Asian cuisine was very nice. Food was also a hot topic to talk about with the locals I quickly discovered.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ordered-Malay-Kebab-at-the-food-court-1-1024x577-640x480.jpg" title="Ordered Malay Kebab at the food court" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>I also enjoyed the sights and food/drinks to try at China Town. The cocktails were as expensive as they would be in Delft.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/On-a-bridge-in-China-Town-1-577x1024-640x480.jpg" title="On-a-bridge-in-China-Town-1" alt="" /></div></div>



<p>Two days before leaving to Singapore, we also visited the butterfly dome in Kuala Lumpur, where many beautiful pictures were taken. Also, we managed to try out the monorail, which was spectacular. The receipt for the ride however was denied when we tried to reimburse it (as public transport costs of the trip), very weird if you ask me.</p>



<div class="wp-block-envira-envira-gallery"><div class="envira-gallery-feed-output"><img class="envira-gallery-feed-image" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/At-the-butterfly-dome-2-1024x768-640x480.jpg" title="At the butterfly dome" alt="" /></div></div><p>The post <a href="/2023/08/11/malaysia-kuala-lumpur/">Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Food-at-Juristech-company-1.mp4" length="6830060" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Post!</title>
		<link>/2023/07/14/first-post/?utm_source=rss#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=first-post</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[danielhonderd]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In just one week, my adventure begins as I embark on a Study Trip organized by my study association. I feel incredibly lucky to be one of the 31 students chosen for this trip across Asia. Our journey will span three weeks, taking us to Kuala Lumpur, Singapore, and Bandung. During our trip, we&#8217;ll have&#8230;&#160;<a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">First Post!</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/">First Post!</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In just one week, my adventure begins as I embark on a Study Trip organized by my study association. I feel incredibly lucky to be one of the 31 students chosen for this trip across Asia. Our journey will span three weeks, taking us to Kuala Lumpur, Singapore, and Bandung.</p>



<p>During our trip, we&#8217;ll have the opportunity to explore fascinating destinations, visit universities and businesses, and immerse ourselves in different cultures. From the bustling streets of Kuala Lumpur to the vibrant city-state of Singapore and the scenic beauty of Bandung, each location promises unique experiences and unforgettable memories.</p>



<p>The Study Visit Committee has meticulously planned our daily itineraries, ensuring a diverse range of activities and excursions. We&#8217;ll have the chance to delve into local cuisines, discover hidden gems, and engage with the vibrant communities we encounter along the way.<br>Additionally, the committee has organized lunch lectures and in-house days at various companies, which not only provide us with valuable insights but also serve as a source of income for part of the trip&#8217;s finances.</p>



<p>As we embark on this journey together, let&#8217;s make it a trip to remember for all the right reasons. From breathtaking sights to enriching cultural encounters, we&#8217;ll seize every moment and create lifelong memories. The countdown has begun, and I can&#8217;t wait to embark on this incredible adventure in just one week&#8217;s time!</p><p>The post <a href="/2023/07/14/first-post/">First Post!</a> first appeared on <a href="/">danielblog</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
